# **Brice Shatzer**

www.BriceShatzer.com

1 W. Superior St. #203 Chicago, IL 60654 brice.shatzer@gmail.com 319-239-2470

Technologist with a decade of experience successfully building software for businesses of various sizes, utilizing dozens of different technologies across the stack. While I specialize in crafting novel user-facing interactions, I have a deep passion for the administrative and organizational processes around the craft of software development.

# Tools & Technologies

#### Currently Using:

- React + Flow
- SASS & LESS
- Jest + Enzyme
- styled-components Git
- Grunt
- PostCSS Node.is • Express.js
- "Vanilla" HTML,
- Babel
- CSS, & Javascript
- PHP
- (WordPress/CraftCMS/Laravel)
- Vue.is
- Karma + Jasmine
- Backbone.is + Marionette
- AngularJS (1.x)
- Underscore.js/Lodash

- AWS Lambda
- Gulp
- jQuery
- GSAP
- Mercurial / SVN
- Apache / NGINX
- Ruby

# Work Experience

# **Software Engineer** — Onion Inc. | G/O Media

September 2017 - Present

- Part of the team that works on Kinja, the CMS that powers some of the internet's favorite sites like Gizmodo, Lifehacker, Kotaku, and The Onion; reaching 85-100 million active users a month
- Helped migrate and rewrite our core platform from a Scala w/ Closure templates back-end & Backbone + Marionette front-end to Isomorphic JavaScript (Express & React)

# **Software Engineer** — Doejo

February 2016 - April 2017

- Handled development of multiple client projects and internal tools across entire stack
- Provided technical advisement to stakeholders throughout the sales and development process
- Served as a resource and mentor for junior developers through pair-programming and code reviews

#### **Web Developer II** — GoHealth Insurance

September 2015 - February 2016

- Created and updated sites used in paid search, display advertising, and affiliate marketing efforts
- Coordinated with external clients to create branded gateways onto a shared Java-powered platform

### **UI/Front-End Developer** — Packback

November 2014 - September 2015

- Designed and implemented responsive views for projects built using AngularJS & Laravel
- Provided updates to Laravel API microservices
- Created front-end build processes in both Grunt and Gulp
- Built and maintained the Bower package used for styling across all company projects

### **Web Developer** — Freelance

August 2014 - July 2015

 Worked with clients to implement new site features and resolve existing issues like cross-browser rendering inconsitencies and front-end build process issues

#### **Web Developer/Designer** — Links Technology Solutions

April 2012 - July 2014

Handled front-end development on multiple client projects across numerous different platforms and technologies.

Education